Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ frankwmeszaros (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Oracle PL/SQL
Relational Databases
Datadog

Languages

German (Elementary)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Frank Meszaros

Systems Engineer at Cloudflare

San Francisco, California, United States

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer and network security industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, HTML, Linux, Amazon Web Services (AWS), and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS). Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science focused in Computer and Information Sciences from The Ohio State University.

Experience

Cloudflare

System Engineer

February 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

- Contributed to UI design and implementation of frontend components into initial CASB offering
- Assisted in design and development of re-architected processing pipeline for scale.

Vectrix (now part of Cloudflare)

Software Engineer

December 2020 - February 2022 (1 year 3 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

- Founding engineer
- Worked closely with founders to build initial product
- Led design and development of initial frontend MVP
- Contributed to design and development of core backend processing pipeline

Finite State

2 years 4 months

Software Engineer

April 2019 - November 2020 (1 year 8 months)

Columbus, Ohio Area

Delivered customer-facing data-driven user interfaces using the React framework.

Led implementation of the Apollo Federated Schema specification so our GraphQL schema could scale across multiple disparate services.

Designed and developed different data modes and GraphQL API schemas to power the core React frontend.

Periodically contributed to different product design ideation sessions.

Software Engineering Intern August 2018 - April 2019 (9 months) Columbus, Ohio Area

Developed admin interface using React to help manage data for initial MVP.

Assisted with developing Apollo GraphQL API using Node.JS.

Capital One Software Engineer Intern June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months) McLean, VA

Assisted in building dashboards for a monitoring and alerting system for team resources hosted on Amazon Web Services (AWS) such as Elastic Container Service (ECS) and Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) as well as monitoring the Docker containers running on each EC2 instance.

Created alerting thresholds for each resource that connected directly to Slack to notify team of any instance that might be at risk.

Tech I worked with:

- Datadog (Client application and API)
- Amazon Web Services
- Docker

The J.M. Smucker Company Solutions Development Intern May 2017 - August 2017 (4 months) Orrville, OH

Deliver design, development, testing, and implementation activities for projects. Create new capabilities, upgrade current systems, and enhance existing projects.

Create and maintain data repositories and master data applications.

Deliver troubleshooting, design, development, testing, and implementation services for production business systems.

The Ohio State University
11 months

Undergraduate Research Assistant April 2017 - August 2017 (5 months)

Columbus, Ohio Area

I assist in Huan Sun's lab with a focus on natural language processing. I am currently helping build a web interface for research participants to annotate datasets and previously helped with annotating a dataset for a Neural Network model designed to create question-answer data objects for coding-oriented questions.

Undergraduate Teaching Assistant January 2017 - May 2017 (5 months) Columbus. Ohio Area

Responsible for grading homework assignments and quizzes.

Holds office hours multiple times a week.

Technology Support Staff October 2016 - January 2017 (4 months) Columbus, Ohio Area

Responsible for providing technology support to departments within the College of Arts and Sciences at The Ohio State University.

Responsibilities include deploying and swapping computers for staff members via Imaging, troubleshooting problems with existing machines on the network, and troubleshooting other technology on the network.

Public Utilities Commission of Ohio Information Technology Intern May 2016 - August 2016 (4 months)

Responsible for providing help desk support within the Commission to employees as needed.

Tasked with deploying and configuring new machines via PC Imaging.

I also helped the development teams on various projects as needed.

Air Force Research Laboratory SPRINT Intern July 2015 - August 2015 (2 months) Dayton, Ohio

I, and five other interns, were assigned a high priority project where we were responsible for planning and developing a virtual program for the National Academy of Sciences that could be distributed on a national level to elementary and middle school students.

Education

The Ohio State University

Bachelor of Science, Computer and Information Sciences · (2015 - June 2019)

Lancaster High School
High School Diploma, High School Diploma with Honors · (2011 - 2015)

Activity

09/13/2023, Viewed by Joeri Leemans